<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://monxd.com/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:54:03 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://monxd.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Write an Async Zsh Prompt</title><link>https://monxd.com/posts/2024-07/write-an-async-zsh-prompt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:54:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://monxd.com/posts/2024-07/write-an-async-zsh-prompt/</guid><description>Why Not Use P10k P10k is a fantastic asynchronous Zsh prompt plugin. It is fast, the author is very active, and it provides convenient customization commands, allowing you to easily generate a Zsh prompt you like. However, when you look at the content of the generated file, it is enormous. This is because the author has provided support for many aspects, such as displaying different language environments, language versions, Git information, prompt formatting, styles, custom function hooks, etc.</description></item><item><title>You Don't Need Nerdfont Patch</title><link>https://monxd.com/posts/2023/12/you-dont-need-nerdfont-patch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 20:09:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://monxd.com/posts/2023/12/you-dont-need-nerdfont-patch/</guid><description>You Don&amp;rsquo;t Need NerdFont Symbol Patch In fact you don&amp;rsquo;t need a font which build with nerd font symbol patch. Nerd font has provide Nerd Fonts Symbols Only font you can only install it. then just use this font for symbols, Use your favorite font for code.
Terminal Config It&amp;rsquo;s easy to config in iterm2,kitty etc modern terminal. Eg i use kitty in arch or mac. In kitty config file you need config symbol map.</description></item><item><title>Neovim Integration Tmux Bar</title><link>https://monxd.com/posts/2023/12/neovim-integra-tmux-bar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 18:50:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://monxd.com/posts/2023/12/neovim-integra-tmux-bar/</guid><description>Introduction Usually I use neovim and tmux in kitty terminal. Currently I use archlinux + hyprland + waybar. There are many status bars on my monitor. neovim statusline and tabline, tmux bar waybar. They overlap in many places and take up my screen space. So I decided to remove some status bars. They are distracting me. I think I can focus on writing code. And I&amp;rsquo;m tired of those status bars with graphical symbols.</description></item><item><title>About &amp;&amp; FAQ</title><link>https://monxd.com/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:37:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://monxd.com/about/</guid><description>Me Hi there is glepnir just a normal guy who is love write code and Open Source :)
Some links of me on top right. Send Email to me
FAQ Language: At present, what I usually write is C C++ Rust Zig Python Go (rarely now) js/ts just some basic react. Any new languages which i insterested, i will learn it and added to this list in the future.
Editor: NeoVim The best editor of the 21st century.</description></item></channel></rss>